>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，欢迎回来。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay,
welcome back from the coercion exercise.
希望你能找到一个有趣的挑战
Hopefully you found that
an interesting challenge.
让我们重新开始，记住阅读过的我说我们想要一个有效的名字函数。
Let's start, again, remember the read me
says we want an is valid name function.
因此，我们将首先定义 isValidName()。
So we'll start by defining isValidName().
它需要命名，它需要声明几个东西。
It needs to take a name, and
it needs to assert several things.
首先，它是一个字符串。
First off, that it is a string.
其次，它至少包含了一些不仅是白色的空间，
Secondly, that it contains at least
something that's not only white space,
它所包含的不是白种空间的东西至少要
and the stuff that it contains that's
not white space has to be at least
三个字好吗
three characters long, okay?
首先，我们要确保输入名称 == "string"。
So first off, we wanna make sure
that the typeof name == "string".
在此我使用的是与运算符类型的双等号，因为我们
Here I'm using the double equals
with the type of operator because we
知道运算符的类型总是返回字符串。
know that the type of operator
always returns strings.
我们知道它总是会返回非空字符串
And we know that it always
returns non-empty strings,
所以如果你愿意的话我们就能安全地走出角落
so we know we're safely out of
the corner cases, if you will.
所以如果 (typeof name == "string")，
So if (typeof name == "string"),
然后， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们也想
and,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We also wanna
确保我们不会只考虑字符串中可能出现的空白
make sure that we don't consider any only
white space that may be in the string,
关于我们的长度检查就是这样
in terms of our length check, that is.
因此，使用 JavaScript 字符串来执行此操作的一个内置方法是修剪方法。
So one built-in way to do that with
JavaScript strings is the trim method.
所以我们可以说如果 name.trim() 在任何重量空间上
So we can say if name.trim(),
which trims off any weight space
从任何一方开始，如果剩下的至少是三种长度的话，
from either side, and if what is
left is at least of length three,
我们就知道有一个有效的字符串
then we know we have a valid string.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我使用的是大于还是大于等于 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Did I use greater than,
or greater than or equal?
嗯，对不起， >= 3，好吗 ?
Yeah, I'm sorry, &gt;= 3, okay?
在这种情况下，我们要返回 true ，否则，我们可以返回 false。
In that case, we wanna return true,
and otherwise we can return false.
现在你可以简化这一点
Now, you could simplify
this a little bit to simply
返回该表达式 ( 如果是您的首选项 ) 。
return that expression if
that's your preference.
您在此处不能有一个 if 语句。
You could not have an if statement here.
只是为了说明我们做出的决定
Just being illustrative of
the decision making that we make,
我们的成功条件是什么
which is are we in a success condition?
太好了，我们回到现实，否则我们就不回来了，我们就会返回 false。
Great, we return true,
otherwise we're not, and we return false.
所以如果我们马上测试这一测试，我们就应该通过测试，
So if we just test this right away,
we should get that test to pass, and
我们应该让这六次测试通过否则一切都不可能成功
we should get these six tests to pass,
and everything else should fail.
我不想出错所以我要定义
I don't wanna get errors,
so I'm gonna just define
一个 hoursAttended() ，并且它没有为我们返回任何内容。
an hoursAttended() and
have it return nothing for us.
所以所有其他的都应该失败。
So all the rest of those should fail.
所以让我们尝试， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 在控制台里。
So let's try,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Over in the console.
再一次，你可以通过节点来运行，如果你觉得更舒适的话。
Again, you could run that via Node,
if that feels more comfortable to you.
但让我们把它在控制台上运行
But let's run it over here in the console,
and
让我们看看它是否显示出我们预期的结果
let's see if it prints out
the results we're expecting.
因此，第一个测试返回 true，这是好的，然后我们有几次失败。
So the first test returns true, which is
good, and then we have several failures.
4 次失败，然后我们有一，二，三，四，五，六次成功，
Four failures, and then we have one, two,
three, four, five, six successes, so
我们看到的是有效的名字通过了我们的测试
we see that is valid name is
passing our test three, okay?
进展不错啊
That's good progress.
让我们一起去个小时
Let's move on to hoursAttended.
现在这个有点复杂但不太重要
Now, this one was a little bit more
complex but not significantly so,
它有两个参数
it takes in two parameters.
记得我们会打电话给那些参加过的人
Remember we're gonna call those attended,
meaning the number of hours that you
参加了一个讲习班，以及讲习班的时间。
attended a workshop, and
the length of the workshop.
现在我们要确保输入的是有效的
Now, we're trying to make sure
that what was inputted is valid,
你参加的时间比参加研讨会的时间不多
that you attended not more hours
than the workshop actually attended,
你不想在那里得到额外的贷款
you don't wanna get extra credit there.
所以我说我们想确保这些都是字符串或数字
So the read me says we wanna make sure
that these are either strings or numbers,
不管他们是什么人我们都要把他们当成数字
and that regardless of which one they
are we're gonna treat them as numbers.
所以如果有人参加的话，我们就想把它变成一个数字，好吗 ?
So if the attended is a string then
we wanna turn it into a number, okay?
首先，我们可以说 ( typeof soteding == "string")。
So first off we could say if
the (typeof attended == "string").
你还记得我要在这里重复检查
And you recall that it's going to,
I'll just double check here.
是啊我们记得我们要确保
Yep, we recall that we need to make sure
我们不能把一个空的字符串变成一个零
that we're not getting an empty
string coerced into a zero,
这不是一个在这里打字的人
cuz that's not the same thing
as somebody typing in zero here.
这就是我们想要照顾的小角落。
So that's a little corner case
that we wanna take care of.
所以我们要说服务员的类型是否为字符串，以及
So we're gonna say if type of
attendant is a string, and
我们要用我们的小伙伴装饰
we're gonna use our
little friend trim again.
Antended.trim() 不等于空字符串。
And attended.trim() is not
equal to empty string.
所以我们不需要任何白色的空间或者空的字符串来适应这里。
So we don't want any white space only or
empty strings to fit in here.
但如果我们有一个非空的字符串，那么我们就开始吧
But if we have a non-empty string,
then let's go ahead and
试着把它变成一个数字
try to make it into a number.
所以我们可以说出席人数 ( 出席人数 ) 。
So here we could say
attended = Number(attended).
这就是我从标准人群中分化的地方比如
Now, here's where I diverge a bit from
standard crowd that, for example,
如静态打字，他们不喜欢将变量重新分配给它的新类型。
like static typing, cuz they don't like
to reassign a variable to its new type.
我认为这是一个完全有效的示例，用于重新分配具有不同变量的变量
I think this is a perfectly valid example
of reassigning variables with a different
类型，当显式地更改某种类型的类型时，就像我们在这里一样。
type, when you are explicitly changing the
type for some purpose, like we are here.
所以这也是为什么
So that's one of the reasons why
我不喜欢当工具向我抱怨重新分配类型时的情况。
I don't like it when tools complain
at me about reassigning over types.
好吧那我们就会做同样的事
Okay, so we're gonna do the same
thing that we just did for attended,
对于长度变量，我们也要这样做。
we also wanna do that for
the length variable.
因此，我将只复制该变量，并将变量更改为长度。
So I will just duplicate that and
change the variable to length.
也许我们可以把它变成一个函数，但是 [SOUND] 谁在乎呢 ?
We could probably factor that out into
a function, but [SOUND] who cares?
好，现在我们知道，如果把它作为一个字符串传入，它就成了一个数字。
Okay, so now we know that if it was passed
in as a string, it has become a number.
如果是一个数字，它仍然是一个数字。
If it was a number, it's still a number.
但我们不知道你在什么地方
But we don't know that you might have
passed in something like null or
未定义，所以我们还是实际需要检查这两者都是数字
undefined, so we still actually need
to check that both of these are numbers
在我们做点什么之前
before we do something.
所以我们首先要说的是
So our check means to first say,
如果输入的类型为 == "number"
if typeof attended == "number"
&& 类型长度 == "number"。
&amp;&amp; typeof length == "number".
如果其中一个不是真的我们会被保释的对吧
If either one of those is not true,
we're gonna bail out, right?
这就是我们的声明
So here is our if statement, and
那我们就得保释期了这就意味着我们要回去了
then we're gonna bail out, and
that means we end up returning false.
这未通过验证。
This didn't pass the validation.
但我们还有更多的需要去检查
But there's more that we need
to check besides just the fact
他们是数字
that they are numbers.
如果你还记得我的话
If you recall in the read me,
说我们想确保他们被视为数字
it said we wanna make sure that
they're treated as numbers.
它们必须是 0 或更高。
They need to be 0 or higher.
所以我们不仅要检查这些数字
So we need to check not
only that they are numbers,
但我们还需要看到有人出席了 > = 0，长度 >= 0。
but we need to also see that
attended &gt;= 0, and length &gt;= 0.
我还说他们需要完整的数字
The read me also says that
they need to be whole numbers,
意味着它们不能像测试用例中的 3.14或 9.1 。
meaning they can't be like 3.14,
or 9.1 as in the test cases.
如果你对 mdn 做了快速检查你可能发现
So if you did a quick check on
mdn you might have found that
专用于 JavaScript 的实用程序。
there is a utility built into
JavaScript specially for this.
它叫做 Number.isInteger ，它告诉我们我们是否有一个东西，是吗 ?
And it's called Number.isInteger, that
tells us if we have a thing that is, yeah?
>> 扬声器 2: 我的意思是，我认为你实际上是把它作为一个数字
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I mean, I think you actually
casted it as a number in the first
部分，对吧 ?
part, right?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的。 >> 扬声器 2:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
他们在后面总是号码很可能是 [ CROSSTALK]
they're are always gonna be numbers
afterwards probably [CROSSTALK]
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 他们是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: They are,
因为如果我在这里过空就不会进这条款了
because if I pass in a null here then
it's not gonna go into this clause and
这里还会是空的
it's gonna still be null here.
>> 扬声器 2: 嗯。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Uh-huh.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以我要去看看
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
that's why I have to check to
确保它实际上是一个数字。
make sure that it's actually a number.
>> 演讲者 2: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
>> Kyle Simpson: 对，我们希望允许字符串和数字，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Right, cuz we want
to allow strings and numbers, but
如果你还有别的事你会失败的如果你愿意的话
if you pass in anything else, you're
gonna fail the validation, if you will.
传递空值将失败验证。
Passing a null fails the validation.
好了我们要检查下是否有一个整数
Okay, so we're gonna check to make sure
that attended is actually an integer.
我们将检查， >> Kyle Simpson: 长度为
And we're gonna check that,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Length is
实际上是一个整数。
actually an integer.
这真的只是说上面没有分数的成分
That really literally just says doesn't
have any fractional component on it,
基本上它在做什么对吗
basically what it's doing, right?
所以查一下那是个数字好吗
So checking that it's a whole number,
all right?
然后读我说的最后一件事
And then the final thing
that the read me says
所参与的值必须小于或等于长度。
is that attended has to be less than or
equal to length.
既然我们知道我们在处理这个问题
Well, since we definitely know we're
dealing with well formed numbers at this
我们没有任何 NN，或者无穷大，或者任何其他的东西。
point, we don't have any NaNs, or
infinities, or any of that other stuff.
对我们来说这是一个非常安全的检查 <= 长度。
Then it's a very safe check for
us to say, attended &lt;= length.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以我们限制了整个地表面积
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we've restricted
the overall surface area that could
可能让我们陷入了转角处
have possibly gotten us into corner cases.
成为一个相当直接的验证集合
Into what is a fairly straightforward
set of checks to validate
我们要通过的就是我们想要传递的东西
that what we're passing in is
what we want to be passed in.
我们正在消灭任何一个角落
And we're eliminating any
of those corner cases,
就像一个人在一个数组中通过一个数字
like somebody passed in
an array with a number in it or
其他的让人喜欢的东西好吗
anything else bonkers like that, okay?
如果我们通过了所有这些检查结果我们就能恢复真实
If we have passed all of these
checks then we can return true,
如果那不合格的话我们就可以回去了
and if that didn't pass,
then we can return false.
和以前一样
Same thing as before,
我们现在可以把它重构为一个回返式的声明
we could now refactor that to
a single return statement.
我只是想让你知道我们如何构建这些测试用例，好吗 ?
I just wanted you to get the point of
how we build up those test cases, okay?
现在让我们在控制台上测试这个代码
So let's now test this
code over in our console,
我们现在就应该得到所有真相
and we should get all trues now, so
运行此代码并获取所有 truees ， yay。
run this code and we get all trues, yay.
好吧我们写了几个验证器函数
All right, so we've written
a couple of validator functions,
想让你熟悉这个想法
point being wanted to get
you familiar with the idea
使用这些原始值以及它们可以被胁迫的方式。
working with these primitive values and
the ways that they can be coerced.
还不能把铁轨关在那些疯狂的角落里
And still not go off the rails
into those crazy corner cases.
保护自己免遭这些角例的侵害。
Protect yourself against
those corner cases.
当然有很多方法可以实现其中的任何一个
There are of course lots of ways that you
could have implemented either one of these
职能。
functions.
不做点长度或检查什么的
Instead of doing a .length or
checking for something,
你可以用正则表达式
you could have used a regular expression.
但它的精神是利用我们对原始类型的了解
But the spirit of this was to use what
we know about primitive types and
关于我们的强制手段的检查好吗
about the checks that our coercion say,
okay?